queryclick.com 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy & Terms and Conditions | QueryClick Limited

## Introduction

This Privacy Notice explains the types of personal data we may collect, how we'll handle it, store it and keep it safe. This notice also tells you about your rights in relation to your personal data.

We hope the following sections will answer any questions you have but if not, please do get in touch with us.   It's likely that we'll need to update this Privacy Notice from time to time. We'll notify you of any significant changes, but you're welcome to come back and check it whenever you wish.  

## Who we are

QueryClick is headquartered at 7 Castle Street, 4th Floor, Edinburgh EH2 3AH, although we also have premises in London. We can be contacted in the following ways:

  * Post: 7 Castle Street, 4th Floor, Edinburgh EH2 3AH
  * Phone: 0131 556 7078
  * Email: [dpo@queryclick.com](mailto:dpo@queryclick.com?Subject=GDPR%20Question%20%5BWebsite%5D "QueryClick GDPR Contact Email")

## What personal data do we process?

We will collect, store and use information about: * our own employees; * prospective employees; * the employees of potential customers and customers; and * the employees of our suppliers.

A separate notice is made available to our employees and prospective employees.

## Why do we process this personal data?

We use the contact details of individual employees to contact them about the work we are doing for them or the work they are doing for us.

We have a legitimate interest to process this information in order to keep doing business. This data will generally be corporate contact details.

We will use these contact details to send information about other products and services from time to time but you will always have the option of telling us not to contact you in this way. If you do not wish to receive this information please let us know using the contact details above.

## Who we share your personal data with

We will only share your personal data as is necessary to provide you with the services that you receive from us or which you provide to us. This will only be with third parties that we trust and where appropriate arrangements are in place.

## Data retention

We will hold your contact details for as long as we are providing your organisation with services or you are providing us with services. If we no longer have this relationship with you we will delete your data after one year.

## Cookies

The internet pages of queryclick.com use cookies. Cookies are small text files that are sent by web servers and stored on visitor's computers so they can be read back at a later date. This is a convenient way of allowing a computer to remember specific information relating to a web site and provide a better user experience. 

The cookies we use on this site are 'analytical' cookies, created by Google Analytics, to track information on your visit. These cookies are unobtrusive and allow both the web site to function and for us to obtain information about the usage of our site, viewing data such as the number of visits, duration of each visit and path taken by the user around the site. This not only allows us to provide an excellent experience but also improves the way our web site works by, for example, making sure users can easily find what they are looking for.

## Your Rights

You have rights in relation to your personal data and can make a request to QueryClick As a data subject, you have a number of rights in relation to your personal data. These are listed in brief below and are set out in more detail in QueryClick's Data Protection Policy/Data Subject Rights Policies. A fee will not generally be charged for exercising any of these rights unless your requests are manifestly excessive.

  * The right to access information about the personal data QueryClick is processing and to obtain a copy of it;
  * The right to require QueryClick to change incorrect or incomplete data;
  * The right to require QueryClick to erase or stop processing your data; and
  * The right to object to the processing of your data where QueryClick is relying on its legitimate interests as the legal ground for processing;

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, or if you have any concerns about how your personal data is being processed, please contact us on the contact details above.

If you still believe that QueryClick has not complied with your rights, you can complain to the Information Commissioner. Contact details are available at www.ico.org.uk
